ACTION SOCIETY uohuus huod
ACTION SOCIETY
ACTION SOCIETY There is but one thing for us to do.
ACTION SOCIETY attack on titan THELAST A TT AC K IN CINEMAS
ACTION SOCIETY
ACTION SOCIETY I hope you will all make the same vow.
ACTION SOCIETY ORIGINAL WORK BY HAJIME ISAYAMA I hope you will all make the same vow.
ACTION SOCIETY ORIGINAL WORK BY HAJIME ISAYAMA To break away from our era of mutual hate..
ACTION SOCIETY To break away from our era of mutual hate...
ACTION SOCIETY
ACTION SOCIETY DIRECTOR YOICHIRO HAYASHI Tell me, Levi. Do you think they're all watching?
ACTION SOCIETY PRODUCTION MAPF
ACTION SOCIETY You think we can stand proud before ourfallen comrades as we are now?
ACTION SOCIETY
ACTION SOCIETY Let's keep fighting all the way to the end
ACTION SOCIETY We're Scout Regiment.. Scouts don't know when to quit.
ACTION SOCIETY
ACTION SOCIETY Give your heart.
Give your heart.
I'm not gonna let you pass!
ACTION SOCIETY I'm not gonna let you pass!
ACTION SOCIETY
ACTION
ACTION SOCIETY Thank you. For showing me what was beyond the walls..
ACTION SOCIETY For showing me this sight.
For showing me this sight.
ACTION SOCIETY SEE FOR YOURSELF We did this.
ACTION SOCIETY Wedid this.
Wedid this.
ACTION SOCIETY We did this.
ACTION SOCIETY THE END
ACTION SOCIETY
ACTION SOCIETY Goodbye, Eren.
ACTION SOCIETY OF THEIR STORY. Goodbye, Eren.
ACTION OCIETY
ACTION SOCIETY E urnf uu yaRhr @Hajime Isayama, KODANSHA/"ATTACK ON TITAN" The Final Season Production Committee
ACTION SOCIETY Eren, thanks forwrapping this scarf around me.
ACTION SOCIETY IN CINEMAS FEBRUARY 26 KODANSHAE C Crunchyroll' SONY