OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERINLAUUER
You know, one of. OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TAINING REASAIUATENY
the scariest-things OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER
when it comes to having 0 OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER TANING RLLACOUE
a conversation OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANING RLLACOUEUA
is engaging. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER
Into small talk.. OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER
A lot of people. OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN IAUDER  CMMRLANAEUSEA
A lot of people. OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERINLAUDIR  jamila_musayeva
are afraid of that. OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERINLAUDIR  TANNRSAEA jamila_musayeva
They try to avoid it. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TUMNG BHIACRUEN jamila_musayeva
They try to avoid it. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AEKIN LAUDER
But we have to learn OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AEKIN LAUDER
how to do it. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANINGHLEALIUEMA
because it's. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANNBI HSALATENA
important parts OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER
of social etiquette. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TUMNGSLSAOUEL
So the tip number one OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TUNNG BILASACIATEALL
that I would tell you OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANMG BLLDACUEA
when it comes to. OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANNG BLASACJAESA
small talk. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER TANAGRLUNAIATENA
is making. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TUNNG RLASAOREUA
give general. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANAGLNAUTN
but specific answers OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANAGRILANAONEL
What I mean by. OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TAMAGRUAURENL
that is OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TAMNG RILASAUAEAY
instead of saying,. OOK BEAUTIFUL O NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANM DLASLURATSY
the weather is so hot OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANM HLASAHATAA
today outside, OOK BEAUTIFUL AERN LAUIER  NG BEAUTIFULLY TUNIM RLTANAURAT
today outside,. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANMRELASATRAR
today outside, OOK BEAUT NG BEAUTIFULLY TANAG RELSAAF
you could say,. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERINLAUDIE  TAMNG BLLSAIAFA
I live in Dubai. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERINLA TAMNG BLLSAA
I ive in Dubai. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY FUNMRULEAE
and the weather is OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERINIAUTIN
super hot there. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERINLAUDIR
super hot there OOK BEAUTIFUL AERINTAUDIE  NG BEAUTIFULLY EUNIN ALP-LO
super hot there. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERINIAUDIE
That gives a clue OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERINLAUDER  TANING RILU-AOO
to your person. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANNRLANAEIO
to your person OOKBEAUT NG BEAUTIFULLY FANNG RELASACHAFU
who you were having OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERINIAIUIR  FANNGRELUSACHAFVA
who you were having OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY ALRINI MLDTR
a conversation with to OOK BEAUTIFUL O NG BEAUTIFULLY AERINIMDTE
then continue. OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANNMLUACHAEDA
on with questions.. OOK BEAUTIFUL  NC BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANNBEESLRIEY
about Dubai. OOK BEAUTIFUL NC BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER
How did you like. OOK BEAUTIFUL  NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANNGHLAACHAEA
living there?. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER TANAGILAACHAE
So on and so forth. OOK BEAUTIFUL NG BEAUTIFULLY AERIN LAUDER  TANAGRELASACHAFNI
So on and so forth. OOK BEAUTIFUL O NG BEALTIFULLY AERN ATTT  CINIMLESRETEE
So on and so forth. OOK BEAUTIFUL I NC.BEAUTIFLLY NAI